Guide to the Lynne Tillman Papers 1939-2008 (Bulk 1984-2006) MSS 180 MSS 180
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XV: Printed Material
  - Printed Mat - Map of Chania Old Town, Undated (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Re:Action - Newsletter of the Neoist Alliance, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - The Red Alert - Tomkins Square Middle School's Red Team, Undated (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Removed from "Code of the Literary Duel", Undated (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Removed from "Fragments toward a Critique of...", Undated (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Removed from "A Life of Secrets", Undated (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Roll Hip Death Press: Gunning for Jesus, Undated (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Rose, Joel - "Kill the Poor" inscribed by author to Lynne Tillman, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Saramago, Jose - "Blindness" advance reading copy, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Sclauzero, Mariarosa - "Marlene" inscribed by author to Lynne Tillman, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Sclauzero, Mariarosa, Coe, Sue - "Narcissism and Death" inscribed, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Sean McDonald (Arcade Publishing) to Lynne Tillman regarding Nuruddin Farah - removed from "Secrets", 1998 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Sheidlower, Jesse ed. - "The F Word", 1995 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Shimada, Masahiko - "Dream Messenger" uncorrected galley proof, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Sirowitz, Hal - "Mother Said" uncorrected proof, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - "Six Pack" 2, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Spanbauer, Tom - "The Man Who Fell in Love with the Moon" inscribed by author to Lynne Tillman, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Stadler, Matthew - "Allan Stein: a novel" uncorrected proof, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Steinke, Rene - "The Fires" uncorrected bound galleys, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Stockholder, Jessica - "Jessica Stockholder", 1992 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Submission to "The Tiger Garden" - removed from front cover, Undated (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Sullivan, Evelin - "The Correspondence" advance page proofs, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - Summers, Anthony - "Goddess: The Secret Lives on Marilyn Monroe" annotated, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Tanzania News Review #39, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Texier, Catherine - "Love Me Tender" inscribed by author to Lynne Tillman, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Tourism Pamphlet - Rottenbuch, Undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Trinidad, David - "Living Doll" with note, Undated (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Trinidad, David - "November" inscribed by author to Lynne Tillman, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Ubbeboda, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Welter, Barbara - "Dimity Convictions: The American Woman in the 19th Century", 1976 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - "Will There Really be a Morning?" - Frances Farmer autobiography, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Williams, Heathcote - "Manifestoes Manifesten" for Franklin Furnace Bookworks exhibit, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Wilson, Martha - "The Book Book" manuscript, Undated (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Woman's Beauty and Health no. 1, 1905 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Woronov, Mary - "Wake for the Angels" unbound, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - "The Writer and his Community" by Chinva Achebe, Undated (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Yablonsky, Linda - "The Story of Junk" New York: Farrar, Straus, and Groux; uncorrected proof, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Zippy Comic Strips - removed from "The Hairy Book", Undated (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Series XVII: Film
  - Series XVII, Subseries A: Film--Access Copies
    Conditions Governing Access
    Access copies do not exist at this time. Please contact a Fales archivist to ask about access to media material.
  - Series XVII, Subseries B: Film--Originals
    - Symbiosis (Box 46, Media ID: 180.0001)
      Format: 16mm
    - Symbiosis - Outs (Box 46, Media ID: 180.0002)
    - Symbiosis - Outs II (Box 46, Media ID: 180.0003)
    - Lynne Tillman Sample Reel - (Committed) (Box 46, Media ID: 180.0004)
    - "Committed" Trailer (Box 46, Media ID: 180.0005)
    - Committed MOS Roll - "Frances' Bedroom" (Box 46, Media ID: 180.0006)
    - Committed - Frances and Psychiatrists (Box 46, Media ID: 180.0007)
    - Committed Mag Track Reel 1 (Box M1, Media ID: 180.0008)
    - Committed Mag Track Reel 2 (Box M1, Media ID: 180.0009)
    - Committed Mag Track Reel 3 (Box M1, Media ID: 180.0010)
    - Earth Angel - Composite Print (Box 47, Media ID: 180.0011)
    - Earth Angel - Workprint (Box 47, Media ID: 180.0012)
    - Videoheads, November 1972 (Box 47, Media ID: 180.0013)
    - Original Family - Workprint (Box 47, Media ID: 180.0014)
    - Dates of a Secretary (Box 46, Media ID: 180.0015)
    - Lynne Tillman - Trims (Box 47, Media ID: 180.0016)
    - Lynne by Tom (Box 47, Media ID: 180.0017)
    - Cats + Austin, 1975 (Box 47, Media ID: 180.0018)
      Format: 8mm
    - [An Empty Room / View from Window] (Box 47, Media ID: 180.0019)
    - Rent Collector #29 (Vintage Porn) (Box 47, Media ID: 180.0020)
    - Sexual Meditation #1 Motel (Box 47, Media ID: 180.0021)
    - F's Dream - Edited Workprint (Box 47, Media ID: 180.0022)
      Format: Super 8mm
    - F's Dream - Gdmother's Hair and Hands (Orig.) (Box 47, Media ID: 180.0023)
    - for F's Dream Sequence [Committed] (Box 47, Media ID: 180.0024)
    - Untitled Workprint [Committed] (Box 47, Media ID: 180.0025)
    - F's Dream - Orig. Super 8 Rolls #3, 4, 5, 6, 7 (Box 47, Media ID: 180.0030, Media ID: 180.0029, Media ID: 180.0028, Media ID: 180.0027, Media ID: 180.0026)
    - F's Dream - Orig. Super 8 Roll #8 (Box 47, Media ID: 180.0031)
      Format: Super 8mm - (color)
    - Super 8mm Roll - Mother + Child (Box 47, Media ID: 180.0032)
    - "Z" For ? [On Beach, ca 1972] (Box 47, Media ID: 180.0033)
    - F's Dream - Trims (Box 47, Media ID: 180.0034)
    - Super 8 Rolls - A, B, C, D, E [Committed] (Box 47, Media ID: 180.0038, Media ID: 180.0039, Media ID: 180.0036, Media ID: 180.0037, Media ID: 180.0035)
    - Sir Winston Churchill -Man and Statesman (Box 48, Media ID: 180.0040)
    - Untitled Copy of Optical Soundtrack (Box 48, Media ID: 180.0041)
      Format: Audiorecording
    - Committed Mix Track Reel 1 and 2 (Box 48, Media ID: 180.0042)
      Format: Magnetic tape
    - Committed Mix Track Reel 3 (Box 48, Media ID: 180.0043)
      Format: Magnetic Tape
    - Unidentified Small Audio Reel (Box 48, Media ID: 180.0044)
      Format: 1/4" Audio
    - Earth Angel (Box 48, Media ID: 180.0045A)
    - Canister- metal box containing Earth Angel Sound ID 180.0045A. Mailed in Holland. (Box 48, Media ID: 180.0045B)
    - Committed Trailer (Box M1, Media ID: 180.0046)
    - Committed Reel 1 (Box M1, Media ID: 180.0047)
    - Committed Reel 2 (Box M1, Media ID: 180.0048)
    - Committed Reel 3 (Box M1, Media ID: 180.0049)
- Series XVIII: Video
  - Series XVIII, Subseries A: Video--Access Copies
  - Series XVIII, Subseries B: Video--Originals
    - Acker (Box 49, Media ID: 180.0050)
      Format: VHS
    - Anne Frank (women who knew her in camp) (Box 49, Media ID: 180.0051)
    - Antoni, Janine. Ready or Not Here I Come., 1994 (Box 49, Media ID: 180.0052)
    - B, Beth. Thanatopsis, Belladonna, Stigmata (Box 49, Media ID: 180.0053)
    - "In the Shadow of the City..." includes appareance by LT (Box 49, Media ID: 180.0054)
    - Bartolomeo, Joel. Mes Videos 91/95 (Box 49, Media ID: 180.0055)
    - Beauty and the Beast (Box 49, Media ID: 180.0056)
    - Bijutsukan, Nichoyou. NHK Channel 3 Nichoyou BIjutsukan on "Beyond the Frame" aired 14 July 1991. (Box 49, Media ID: 180.0057)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      Broken
    - Cixous, Helene and Paul Ricoeur. Talking Liberties. (Box 49, Media ID: 180.0058)
    - Come and Get It (Box 49, Media ID: 180.0059)
    - Corpuz, Jimi. (Box 49, Media ID: 180.0060)
    - Currents '93: Dress Codes. Produced by The Institute of Contemporary Art, Boston. (Box 49, Media ID: 180.0061)
    - Dooley, Shannon Massie. Madame Realism in Freud's Dreamland: video collection of postcards interpreted by Shannon Massie Dooley. (Box 49, Media ID: 180.0062)
    - Faber, Mindy. Delirium. (Box 49, Media ID: 180.0063)
    - Fiskin, Judy. Diary of a Midlife Crisis. (Box 49, Media ID: 180.0064)
      FOrmat: VHS
    - Gilooley, Jane. MacDowell December 1995-January 1996. (Box 49, Media ID: 180.0065)
    - Ha, Minh. Living is Round. (Box 49, Media ID: 180.0066)
    - Hartley, Pat. Hung Up. (Box 49, Media ID: 180.0067)
    - Hartley, Pat. Relationships. (Box 49, Media ID: 180.0068)
    - Hellzapoppin'/ Lou Reed Amnesty International 15 June 1986. (Box 49, Media ID: 180.0069)
    - Hiller, Susan. Part 1, exerpt from broadcast television. Gallery discussion of "Secret Wars" 1990. (Box 49, Media ID: 180.0070)
    - Hiller, Susan. Part 2, excerpts from broadcast television. 1. Panel Discussion, The Late Show 1989 2. Interview, Wide Angle 1989 (Box 49, Media ID: 180.0071)
    - Hiller, Susan. "S. Hiller on TV" (Box 49, Media ID: 180.0072)
    - Hollywood and Jews, A&E documentary, 22 March 1998. (Box 49, Media ID: 180.0073)
    - Holocaust Museum documentary, FDR and the Holocaust. (Box 49, Media ID: 180.0074)
    - "Honest Answers" and "Home on the Web" (Box 49, Media ID: 180.0075)
    - "Housesitter" with Steve Martin and Goldie Hawn. (Box 49, Media ID: 180.0076)
    - Kalin, Tom. Exerpts from Third Known Nest (1991-1995). (Box 49, Media ID: 180.0077)
    - Kobland, Ken. Berlin: Tourist Journal, 1988. (Box 50, Media ID: 180.0078)
    - Koppel, 16 March 1989, "Mommy Track" Koppel, 4 April 1989, Pollard Daryl Yates Rist, 5 APril 1989, 11th St Jean Harris, 18 April 1989 (Box 50, Media ID: 180.0079)
    - Kuchar, George. The Unclean. (Box 50, Media ID: 180.0080)
    - MacDowell 1 Nov.-20 Dec 2001 (Box 50, Media ID: 180.0081)
    - Marilyn. (Box 50, Media ID: 180.0082)
    - Media Show. (Box 50, Media ID: 180.0083)
    - The Media Show. International Show Reel 2. (Box 50, Media ID: 180.0084)
    - Media Show. (Box 50, Media ID: 180.0085)
    - The Media Show: General Compliation Series II. (Box 50, Media ID: 180.0086)
    - Meiwa-Denki. NTV "Neo Hyper Kids" 1996. (Box 50, Media ID: 180.0087)
    - Milosovic, Frontline story. (Box 50, Media ID: 180.0088)
    - Municipal Arts, 6 October 1999. (Box 50, Media ID: 180.0089)
    - Norman, Jessye. "Recording Carmen" (Box 50, Media ID: 180.0090)
    - OJ Verdict (Box 50, Media ID: 180.0091)
    - OJ (Box 50, Media ID: 180.0092)
    - OJ (Box 50, Media ID: 180.0093)
    - OJ (Box 50, Media ID: 180.0094)
    - Obrist, Hans Ulrich. "ett projekt av/a project" (Box 50, Media ID: 180.0095)
    - Rainer, Yvonne. Compilation Tape, 1997. (Box 50, Media ID: 180.0096)
    - Robert F. Kennedy and Martin Luther King, Persepctive, 21 June 1998. (Box 50, Media ID: 180.0097)
    - Scott, James. A Shocking Accident. 1984. (Box 50, Media ID: 180.0098)
    - Sone, Yutaka. Her 19th Foot. (Box 50, Media ID: 180.0099)
    - Said, Edward; Terry Eagleston; Jacques Derrida. Talking Liberties. (Box 50, Media ID: 180.0100)
    - Takashimaya. The Gallery. 22 May 1993. (Box 50, Media ID: 180.0101)
    - Thomas/Hill. 12 October 1991. (Box 50, Media ID: 180.0102)
    - Thornton, Leslie and Ron Vawter. Remembering Ron: Strange Space. (Box 50, Media ID: 180.0103)
    - Tillman, Lynne. Reading at Biblios, 23 March 1995. (Box 50, Media ID: 180.0104)
    - Tillman, Lynne. Die Mieterin/Haunted Houses, German TV. (Box 51, Media ID: 180.0105)
    - Tillman, Lynne. Die Mieterin/Haunted Houses, N-TV-Bucher, 1998. (Box 51, Media ID: 180.0106)
    - Tillman, Lynne. Motion Sickness and To FInd Words. October 1991 reading in Blacksburg, VA. (Box 51, Media ID: 180.0107)
    - Tillman, Lynne. No Lease on Life, German Television. (Box 51, Media ID: 180.0108)
    - Tillman, Lynne. North Haven Library Bookstore Reading, 9 August 2001. (Box 51, Media ID: 180.0109)
    - Tillman, Lynne. St Marks 1 January 1989 Reading. (Box 51, Media ID: 180.0110)
    - Tillman, Lynne. Spectacolor. (Box 51, Media ID: 180.0111)
    - Tillman, Lynne. Ziggy. (Box 51, Media ID: 180.0112)
    - Tillman, Lynne. Reading, 1998. (Box 51, Media ID: 180.0113)
    - Tonoshiki, Tadashi. Reversing Reality. (Box 51, Media ID: 180.0114)
    - Transmigration part 1-3, 1986-1989. (Box 51, Media ID: 180.0115)
    - TV Museum- Public Art in Tameike-sanno Station" 4 October 1997. (Box 51, Media ID: 180.0116)
    - Video nation Uncut. (Box 51, Media ID: 180.0117)
    - Warmis, Carolyn. (Box 51, Media ID: 180.0118)
    - Wexner Prize Lecture, 18 May 1995. Tape 1 of 2. (Box 51, Media ID: 180.0119)
    - Wexner Prize Lecture, 18 May 1995. Tape 2 of 2. (Box 51, Media ID: 180.0120)
    - What Does She Want. Program 1: We Ae Not Sugar and Spice and Everything Nice. Program notes by Lynne Tillman. (Box 51, Media ID: 180.0121)
    - What Does She Want. Program 2: Bat Attitude. Program notes by Lynne Tillman. (Box 51, Media ID: 180.0122)
    - What Does She Want. Program 3: Fact is Stranger than Fiction. Program notes by Lynne Tillman. (Box 51, Media ID: 180.0123)
    - What Does She Want. Program 4: A Crack in the Tube. Program notes by Lynne Tillman. (Box 51, Media ID: 180.0124)
    - What Does She Want. Program 5: Variety Is the Spice of Life. Program notes by Lynne Tillman. (Box 51, Media ID: 180.0125)
    - What Does She Want. Program 6: Women With a Past. Program notes by Lynne TIllman. (Box 51, Media ID: 180.0126)
    - Non-Roman alphabet label. (Box 51, Media ID: 180.0127)
    - Non-Roman alphabet label. (Box 51, Media ID: 180.0128)
- Series XIX: Audio
  - Series XIX, Subseries A: Audio--Access Copies
  - Series XIX, Subseries B: Audio--Originals
    Cassettes 180.0129 - 180.0221 we received in a box labeled "Bookstore". These tapes are arranged alphabetically.
    - Allen, Woody, 4/29/98 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0129)
      Format: Audiocassette
    - Aronson, Steven, 1/21/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0130)
    - Auster, Paul, 1/2/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0131)
    - Auster, Paul, 2/17/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0132)
    - Barliant, Dan - Barbara's Bookstore, 4/21/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0133)
    - Bentley, Duncan, 5/5/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0134)
    - Benton, Robert, Undated (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0135)
    - Bergen, Andrew, 11/11/96 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0136)
    - Bernhard, Lisa, 4/15/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0137)
    - Bloodworth, Penelope, 4/7/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0138)
    - Blount Jr., Roy, 2/16/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0139)
    - Bogner, Elizabeth, 2/27/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0140)
    - Books & Co., 1/30/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0141)
    - Cash, Francis, 2/23/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0142)
    - Castberry, May, 12/10/96 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0143)
    - Chase, Lynn, 1/30/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0144)
    - Cheener, Susan, 4/8/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0145)
    - Contant, Bob, Terry ? - St. Marks Books, 4/22/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0146)
    - Cunningham, Michael, 4/28/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0147)
    - Dale, Clara, 3/27/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0148)
    - Falkin, James, 4/16/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0149)
    - Feder, Jenny - Three Lives Bookstore, 4/17/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0150)
    - Ford, C.H., 1/30/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0151)
    - Galassi, Jonathan, 3/14/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0152)
    - Ghiz, Margie - Midnight Special Bookstore, 5/15/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0153)
    - Gill, Brendan, 1/13/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0154)
    - Gimbel, Wendy; Ascher, Barbara Lazear, 4/22/97 - 4/24/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0155)
    - Hadley, Leila, 12/11/96 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0156)
    - Haien, Jeannette, 12/10/96 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0157)
    - Hanhardt, John, 12/12/96 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0158)
    - Hartley, Pat, Undated (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0159)
    - Hempel, Amy, Undated (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0160)
    - Hitchcock, Janey, 4/23/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0161)
    - Houston, Scott - Phone Message, 4/12/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0162)
    - Houston, Scott; Hall, Julie Ann, 2/27/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0163)
    - Howard, Richard, 3/14/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0164)
    - Hawarth, Richard - Square Books, Oxford, Miss, 4/12/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0165)
    - Jeanette III, Oct. 8, 1996 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0166)
    - Jeanette (4), Undated (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0167)
    - Jeanette - bits, 5/5/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0168)
    - Jeanette at Books & Co., 1/14/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0169)
    - Jeanette - scrapbooks, 5/16/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0170)
    - Jeanette - scrapbooks, 5/12/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0171)
    - Jeanette - scrapbooks, 5/22/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0172)
    - Jeanette Sept 30 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0173)
    - Jeanette at Stowe, 3/18/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0174)
    - Jeanette at Stowe, 3/18/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0175)
    - Jeanette at Stowe, 3/19/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0176)
    - Jeanette at Stowe, 3/20/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0177)
    - K., Richie, Undated (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0178)
    - Kaplan, Max V., 4/4/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0179)
    - Lauterbach, Ann, 12/11/96 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0180)
    - Leibowitz, Fran, 12/11/96 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0181)
    - Lyons, Donald, Undated (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0182)
    - McClatchy, JD, 5/19/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0183)
    - Mead, Taylor, Undated (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0184)
    - Moonen, Ted, 6/8/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0185)
    - Moreau, Jeanne, 4/16/97 (Box 52, Cassette ID: 180.0186)
    - Moreau, Jeanne - NY1, Channel 4 news, Undated (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0187)
    - Morris, Debi - Barbara's Bookstore; Kaplan, Mitchell - Books and Books, 4/17/97 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0188)
    - Murray, Albert, 12/6/96 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0189)
    - O'Brien, Edna, May 15, 1997 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0190)
    - Phillbrook, Peter, 11/11/96 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0191)
    - Phillbrook, 12/10/96 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0192)
    - Phillbrook, Peter, 3/21/97 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0193)
    - Pomeranz, Bud, 1/21/97 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0194)
    - Powell, Michael, 4/30/97 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0195)
    - Rabinowitz, John, 12/2/96 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0196)
    - Ross, David, 11/5/97 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0197)
    - Sanger, Alex, 4/14/97 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0198)
    - Sanger, Alex, 5/1/97 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0199)
    - Schama, Simm, 5/5/98 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0200)
    - Schenk, Ginette; Tillman, Lynne; Stockholder, Jessica, 3/26/95 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0201)
    - Scott, Susan, Undated (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0202)
    - Silverberg, Ira, 2/10/97 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0203)
    - Slovak, Paul, Undated (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0204)
    - Slovak, Paul, Undated (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0205)
    - Solowitz, Ed, Undated (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0206)
    - Sontag, Susan, 4/1/98 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0207)
    - Spivey, Alexandra Anderson, 3/5/97 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0208)
    - Trillin, Calvin, 1/28/97 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0209)
    - Trillin, Calvin, 6/29/97 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0210)
    - Unowsky, David - Hungry Mind Bookstore, 4/30/97 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0211)
    - Varni, Steven, 3/6/97 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0212)
    - Varni, Steven - on Whitney, 6/5/97 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0213)
    - Watson, Jeanette, 9/20/96 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0214)
    - Watson, Jeanette - signed books, 4/18/97 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0215)
    - Watson, Olive, 4/24/97 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0216)
    - Weld, Jackie, 1/14/97 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0217)
    - Wilentz, Ted, Undated (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0218)
    - Wilson, Martha, 3/24/97 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0219)
    - Yau, John, 2/12/97 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0220)
    - Yamizaki, Paul - City Lights Bookstore, 5/1/97 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0221)
    - Allen, Woody and A. Shaw, Undated (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0222)
    - Ans. Machine - Patrick and Colm on No Lease on Life; Ira singing Happy Birthday; C. Trillin - Jill Goldenberg, 1998 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0223)
    - Aronowitz, Dec. 7 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0224)
    - Aronowitz, Dec. 7 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0225)
    - Ashbery, John, Undated (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0226)
    - Baldwin, Gordon, Undated (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0227)
    - Baldwin Seminar - Craig Owens, 4/14/86 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0228)
    - Baldwin Seminar - Craig Owens, 4/15/86 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0229)
    - Baldwin Seminar - Craig Owens, 4/17/86 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0230)
    - Baldwin Seminar - Craig Owens, 4/18/86 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0231)
    - BBC Radio 4 - Open Book, 24/05/98 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0232)
    - Bensman - Chinese Literature, Nov. 15 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0233)
    - Bensman and Lynne Tillman, Nov. 15 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0234)
    - Bensman and Lynne Tillman - Chinese Literature, Nov. 15 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0235)
    - Books & Co. on WNYC, 10/6/99 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0236)
    - Book Show #507, 3/31/98 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0237)
    - Bookworm, 4/24/91 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0238)
    - Bookworm recorded, 3/3/98 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0239)
    - Bookworm recorded, 3/3/03 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0240)
    - Bookworm - Lynne Tillman, 06/05/03 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0241)
    - Bottomly, Susan, Undated (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0242)
    - Brandauer, Klaus Maria, Undated (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0243)
    - Brown class, 4/3/90 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0244)
    - Brown, M., 4/24/90 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0245)
    - Brown, 4/24/30 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0246)
    - Brown, Mike, 4/17/90 (Box 35, Cassette ID: 180.0247)
    - Brown, Mike, 5/8/90 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0248)
    - Brown, Mike, 5/1/90 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0249)
    - Buhl, Henry, Dec. 14, 1999 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0250)
    - Cale, John, 12/3/93 (Box 53, Cassette ID: 180.0251)
    - Cale, John; Tillman, Lynne, Undated (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0252)
    - Canada Radio, March 10 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0253)
    - Commodity Group, 1/4/90 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0254)
    - Dreher, Peter; Tillman, Lynne, Undated (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0255)
    - Fields, Danny, Undated (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0256)
    - Fields, Danny - New Xerox, Undated (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0257)
    - Ford, C.H., 3/4/90 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0258)
    - Ford, C.H. - int. Dakota, Jan. 2001 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0259)
    - Foreman, Amanda - Elle (NT), 1999 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0260)
    - Forman - Acker: RF, Undated (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0261)
    - Geldzahler, Henry, 12/7/92 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0262)
    - Giardinelli, Mempo, 10/10/98 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0263)
    - Giardinelli, Mempo, 10/10/98 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0264)
    - Green, Sam, Undated (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0265)
    - Harris, Les, Undated (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0266)
    - Harris, Les, Undated (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0267)
    - Haynes, Jim - from Paris, Undated (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0268)
    - Hughes, Fred - Tour; Sasha Chermaye[l], Feb. 2000 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0269)
    - Jeanette telling me that Richard Howard loves me..., 1997 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0270)
    - Jessica II, Undated (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0271)
    - JS/LT - Julia Scher, Lynne Tillman, Undated (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0272)
    - Kahn, Stanya, 12/5/01 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0273)
    - Kiernan, Frances, Jan. 3, 2000 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0274)
    - Kiki; Lynne Tillman, 9/4/03 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0275)
    - Jay, Martin - Lacan and Vision, New School, 10/27/90 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0276)
    - Lynne's Reading - Ear Inn, 1978 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0277)
    - Lyons, Donald, Undated (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0278)
    - M., Gerard, Undated (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0279)
    - Mallanga, G., Undated (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0280)
    - Marx, Jan. 4, 1990 (Box 54, Cassette ID: 180.0281)